[{"answer": "0 each morning.  He hates getting up early an", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 6, "question": "", "qSentId": 5},{"answer": " Good morning Sam", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 11, "question": "0 each morning.  He hates getting up early an", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Hi, Mom", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 12, "question": " Good morning Sam", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " What do you want for breakfast this morning", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Hi, Mom", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Mom, you know I dont like to eat breakfast.  Im too tired to eat anything.  Im no", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 14, "question": " What do you want for breakfast this morning", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " You need to eat breakfast, Sam.  Its important", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Mom, you know I dont like to eat breakfast.  Im too tired to eat anything.  Im no", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Why is it so important?  Im always fine without it", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 19, "question": " You need to eat breakfast, Sam.  Its important", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " You keep telling me that youre tired and hungry at school.  You told me that yo", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Why is it so important?  Im always fine without it", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Yeah, so", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 24, "question": " You keep telling me that youre tired and hungry at school.  You told me that yo", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Well, it could be because youre not eating breakfast.  Youre not getting enoug", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Yeah, so", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " I doubt it", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Well, it could be because youre not eating breakfast.  Youre not getting enoug", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Really, Sam.  Breakfast is the most important meal of the day", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 32, "question": " I doubt it", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Why", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Really, Sam.  Breakfast is the most important meal of the day", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Because in the morning, youve been sleeping for a long time and your bod", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Why", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Thats probably just an old wives tale, Mom", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Because in the morning, youve been sleeping for a long time and your bod", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " No, Sam.  That information comes from doctors.  Studies have shown that kid", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Thats probably just an old wives tale, Mom", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Yeah, right", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 44, "question": " No, Sam.  That information comes from doctors.  Studies have shown that kid", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Look, even if you dont believe me you need to eat breakfast.  What do yo", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Yeah, right", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " No, I hate cereal.  All you buy is the gross kind", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Look, even if you dont believe me you need to eat breakfast.  What do yo", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " OK, do you want toast or a bagel", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 50, "question": " No, I hate cereal.  All you buy is the gross kind", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " No, I dont think either of those sound good either.  I dont want bread", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 51, "question": " OK, do you want toast or a bagel", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " All right, how about eggs", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 52, "question": " No, I dont think either of those sound good either.  I dont want bread", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Fine, Ill have eggs", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 53, "question": " All right, how about eggs", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " OK.  How do you want them cooked?  Do you want fried eggs, scrambled eggs", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Fine, Ill have eggs", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " An omelet, I guess", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 58, "question": " OK.  How do you want them cooked?  Do you want fried eggs, scrambled eggs", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " What do you want in it?  We have peppers, mushrooms, bacon, or ham", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 59, "question": " An omelet, I guess", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Umm. Ham and mushrooms", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 60, "question": " What do you want in it?  We have peppers, mushrooms, bacon, or ham", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " All right.  Ill make that for you.  Make sure you eat some fruit and drink som", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Umm. Ham and mushrooms", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Fine, Ill have a banana.  Can I have some coffee", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 65, "question": " All right.  Ill make that for you.  Make sure you eat some fruit and drink som", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Coffee?  Since when do you like coffee", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Fine, Ill have a banana.  Can I have some coffee", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " The kids at school go to Starbucks and hang out, mom", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Coffee?  Since when do you like coffee", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Well, youre not having coffee at home.  Its not good for a young boy who is stil", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 71, "question": " The kids at school go to Starbucks and hang out, mom", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " But, Mom", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Well, youre not having coffee at home.  Its not good for a young boy who is stil", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Sam, I said no.  Now thats the end of it", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 76, "question": " But, Mom", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Fine, Ill just have a glass of milk", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Sam, I said no.  Now thats the end of it", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Good.  You need to have a healthy meal in the mornings.  It will give you th", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Fine, Ill just have a glass of milk", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Good.  You need to have a healthy meal in the mornings.  It will give you th", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Heres your omelet.  Do you want ketchup", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 83, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " No, thanks", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Heres your omelet.  Do you want ketchup", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Im glad youre trying to eat breakfast, Sam.  I think youll feel better at school", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 85, "question": " No, thanks", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Maybe.  Well see", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Im glad youre trying to eat breakfast, Sam.  I think youll feel better at school", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Theres the bus.  Youd better run.  Dont forget your lunch", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Maybe.  Well see", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Thanks, mom.  See ya", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Theres the bus.  Youd better run.  Dont forget your lunch", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Bye, honey.  Have a nice day at school", "docId": "10-07", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Thanks, mom.  See ya", "qSentId": 88}]
